bandelal.com 2012-11-20

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. The privacy of the users is vital to us. So BandeLal has developed this privacy policy to explain to the users the workings of this website that is, how we collect, use and protect the users' information and data. This privacy policy is applicable for all BandeLal websites and their affiliate websites. We reserve the right to update the privacy policy as and when required. So users are requested to keep an eye on the latest versions of the privacy policy at our websites from time to time. By using BandeLal.com you agree to abide by the terms and conditions of our privacy policy and that you acknowledge the possibility of changes in the privacy policy in future. 

**Collection**

* * *

Information and data posted at BandeLal are publicly available. BandeLal servers are located in various Indian cities. So whenever you provide us any information and data you agree to the storage and transfer of that information on BandeLal servers in different cities. BandeLal collects and stores the following kinds of personal information: 

Email address, contact information such as phone numbers and address and financial information (if necessary). 

Other information such as IP address of users and various necessary web log information. 

Computer sign-in data, site statistics and users' on page views and visits, advertisement data, traffic to and from BandeLal. 

(All these information are collected through cookies. The users can disable the cookies on their browsers if they wish but cookie disabling may impact the ability to use the website.) 

**Use**

* * *

BandeLal uses personal information for:

Providing services   
Collecting fees, troubleshooting problems, resolving dispures  
Safe and secure trading   
Enforcement of our policies  
For informing the users about products, services, policies, events and updates   
Customization as per users' requirements  
Promoting user-friendly experience  
Promotion of our products and services  
Providing various offers and discounts  
Collection of necessary information and data   
Our promotional communications via emails, sms, phone. 

**Disclosure**

* * *

We do not reveal any personal information to third parties that could be used to identify you personally such as your bank account number, credit card number, passwords etc. 

We shall not sell or rent our users' personal information to external organizations or third parties without users' consent. 

All user data and information at BandeLal.com are highly confidential and BandeLal shall not disclose such information to third parties and external organizations. 

We may disclose users' personal information to governmental and law enforcing agencies as and when required but we will do so with strict care and under proper authorities. 

We may reveal our users' personal information to investigation and law enforcement authorities for legal procedures in case of fraud, faulty transactions, violation of others' rights and safety. 

We may reveal our users' personal information to our service providers, corporate partners and corporate affiliates with our users' consent. 

We do not disclose personal information of one user to other user/users. No personal information is disclosed by us without prior user consent. 

**Access, Editing and Deleting**

* * *

You have complete access and control over your personal data and information at our site. You can view, edit or delete your personal information by reviewing and reconsidering your account page and postings. 

For revising and modifying any personal information that is not available for viewing at BandeLal.com you can simply contact our customer support team via phone calls, emails or sms. 

When you delete your account, your personal information stored at our servers gets deleted automatically after a certain period. Personal information gets deleted when it is no longer required. 

**Data Security**

* * *

We ensure that your personal information is safe and secure with us. We have several tools and technologies to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, misuse, loss or disclosure. We have online security systems, encryption and passwords to protect your personal information. 

But online information transmission cannot be guaranteed to be 100% safe and secure. So you are responsible for any information that you provide to us. Once you provide us with your personal information we take all the possible steps to protect that information. 

**Information Confidentiality**

* * *

By using BandeLal.com services, features and products users acknowledge that they are aware of and shall abide by the terms and conditions of our privacy policy. 

The users are responsible for any information that they provide to us.

The users are responsible for the postings they provide on our sites and must be ready to face the consequences of those postings.
